[
    {
        "question": "Q1: CSS stands for -",
        "a":"Cascade style sheets",
        "b":"Color and style sheets",
        "c":"Cascading style sheets",
        "d":"None of these",
        "ans":"ans3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q2: The property in CSS used to change the background color of an element is -",
        "a":"bgcolor",
        "b":"color",
        "c":"background-color",
        "d":"All of the above",
        "ans":"ans3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q3: The CSS property used to control the element's font-size is -",
        "a":"text-style",
        "b":"text-size",
        "c":"font-size",
        "d":"None of the above",
        "ans":"ans3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q4: The HTML attribute used to define the inline styles is -",
        "a":"style",
        "b":"styles",
        "c":"class",
        "d":"None of the above",
        "ans":"ans1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q5: Which of the following CSS property is used to set the background image of an element?",
        "a":"background-attachment",
        "b":"background-image",
        "c":"background-color",
        "d":"None of the above",
        "ans":"ans2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q6: Which of the following is the correct syntax to make the background-color of all paragraph elements to yellow?",
        "a":"p {background-color : yellow;}",
        "b":"p {background-color : #yellow;}",
        "c":"all {background-color : yellow;}",
        "d":"all p {background-color : #yellow;}",
        "ans":"ans1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q7: Which of the following property is used as the shorthand property for the padding properties?",
        "a":"padding-left",
        "b":"padding-right",
        "c":"padding",
        "d":"All of the above",
        "ans":"ans3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q8: The CSS property used to make the text bold is -",
        "a":"font-weight : bold",
        "b":"weight: bold",
        "c":"font: bold",
        "d":"style: bold",
        "ans":"ans1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q9: Are the negative values allowed in padding property?",
        "a":"Yes",
        "b":"No",
        "c":"Can't say",
        "d":"May be",
        "ans":"ans2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Q10: Which of the following property is used as the shorthand property of margin properties?",
        "a":"margin-left",
        "b":"margin-right",
        "c":"margin",
        "d":"None of the above",
        "ans":"ans3"
    }
]